Finding Aid for Dept. of Biology (University of Michigan) Records 1879-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Promotions 1960-1985
  - General
    - 1964 (Box 18)
    - 1965 (Box 18)
    - 1966 (Box 18)
    - 1967 (Box 18)
    - 1968 (Box 18)
    - 1969 (Box 18)
    - 1970 (Box 18)
    - 1971 (Box 18)
    - 1972 (Box 18)
    - 1973 (Box 18)
    - 1974 (Box 18)
    - 1975 (Box 18)
    - 1976 (Box 18)
    - 1977 (Box 18)
    - 1978 (Box 18)
    - 1979 (Box 18)
    - 1980, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - 1981 (Box 18)
    - 1982 (Box 18)
    - 1983, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - 1984, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - 1985, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - 1986, 2 folders (Box 19)
      [RESTRICTED until 7/1/2016 ]
    - 1987-1988 (Box 19)
      [RESTRICTED until 7/1/2018 ]
    - 1988-1989 (Box 19)
      [RESTRICTED until 7/1/2019 ]
  - Promotions Committee
    - 1975-1976 (Box 19)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 19)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 19)
    - 1979-1980, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 20)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 20)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 20)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 20)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 20)